contestblogger.com 2008-07-08

# Contest Blogger Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

**This privacy policy and disclaimer applies to all of the following websites:**

The privacy of your personal information is important to us. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit our websites, and how we safeguard your information. We never share or sell your personal information or email addresses to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our websites and which pages you visited throughout our websites.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our websites. This could include the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on to support our websites. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our websites, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our websites, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.  **Because our websites are monetized using Google Adsense, you can find a list of current Google third party ad providers below.**

List provided courtesy of [blogsblogsblogs.com](http://google-third-party-ads.blogsblogsblogs.com/)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in security programs. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our websites as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Other Important Information**

Our websites are intended only for people who are eighteen (18) years of age or older. We are NOT responsible for the privacy policies of websites, blogs and pages linked to anywhere on our websites. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our websites, or about our privacy policy or the safety of your private information when you visit ourwebsites, please contact us by using our [contact form](http://www.contestblogger.com/submit-a-contest-project-or-comment/).

**Important Disclaimer**

Our websites, their webmaster, hosting service and administrators do not create, run, take part in, endorse, recommend or approve of any of the contests, sweepstakes, giveaways, free samples, offers, programs, games, software, graphics, coupons or websites listed, linked to or referred to on our websites.

It is your responsibility to determine the validity and safety of each offer. Our websites, their webmaster, hosting service and administrators are not responsible for any loss of funds, property, information or time resulting from taking part in contests, sweepstakes, giveaways, programs and offers on our websites, from visiting websites linked to on these sites, or from downloading software, programs, and files linked to on these sites.
